With This Ring is a romance, comedy, tv movie film directed by Nzingha Stewart.
After attending their friend Elise's wedding to Nate on New Year's Eve, Trista, a career-­driven talent agent, Viviane, a successful gossip
columnist, and Amaya, a struggling actress, make a pact to get married within the year to either a new love or a man waiting in the wings.
But the close friends face their own set of challenges - Trista has not gotten over her commitment-­phobic ex-­boyfriend Damon, Viviane is secretly in love
with Sean, the father of her son, and Amaya is desperate to break up her boyfriend Keith's unhappy marriage so they can live happily ever after.
Each woman starts the year with high hopes and dreams of
what will happen over the next 12 months...
but will they all make it to the altar?
Trista, played by Regina Hall.
Viviane, played by Jill Scott.
Eve, played by Eve.
Elise, played by Brooklyn Sudano.
Keith, played by Deion Sanders.
Nate, played by Stephen Bishop.
With This Ring is an American romantic comedy drama
television film that aired on Lifetime in 2015.
Written and directed by Nzingha Stewart, it stars
Regina Hall, Jill Scott and Eve.
Stewart adapted the script from the 2006 novel The Vow by
Denene Millner, Angela Burt-Murray and Mitzi Miller.
The film explores themes of new year's eve, based on novel or book,
ex-boyfriend, female friendship, relationship problems.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.